Russel Wright Papers
Russel Wright Papers
- Clients and products
  - Forster Textiles
    - Design, color, 2 folders (Box 13)
    - Gold jacquard (Box 13)
    - Ideas (Box 13)
    - Jacquard, 3 folders (Box 13)
  - Fostoria Glass Company
    - Colored glass windows (Box 13)
    - Designs selected (Box 13)
    - Drawings, 5 folders (Box 13)
    - Materials and data (Box 13)
    - Renderings (Box 13)
    - Trip (Box 13)
  - Foundation drawing (Garrison House) (Box 13)
  - Four Seasons (Box 13)
  - Furniture cut-outs
    - Bedroom (Box 13)
    - Dining room (Box 13)
    - Living room (Box 13)
    - Miscellaneous juvenile (Box 13)
  - Furniture details (Box 14)
  - Garden seat (Box 14)
  - General American Transportation Company
    - Bread and butter (Box 14)
    - B-cup (Box 14)
    - Cover - vegetable bowl (Box 14)
    - Creamer (Box 14)
    - Cup studies (Box 14)
    - Dinnerware (Box 14)
    - Drawings, 2 folders (Box 14)
    - Fruit (Box 14)
    - Pattern templates (Box 14)
    - Patterns (Box 14)
    - Patterns - templates (Box 14)
    - Plates (Box 14)
    - Plates, lip details (Box 14)
    - Preliminary studies (Box 14)
    - Research, clocks (Box 14)
    - Saucer (Box 14)
    - Soup bowl (Box 14)
  - General Electric Company (GE)
    - Clock, 2 folders (Box 14)
    - Conference
      - Ceramic clock (Box 14)
      - Estimates (Box 14)
      - Factory notes (Box 14)
    - Design
      - Ceramic shapes (Box 14)
      - Clock preliminary design, 2 folders (Box 14)
      - Clock sketches (Box 14)
      - Study #6 (Box 14)
      - New sketches (Box 14)
      - Numeral studies, 2 folders (Box 14)
      - Rejected by us (Box 14)
      - Templates (Box 14)
      - Wood clock (Box 14)
    - Drafting
      - Ceramic clock, 2 folders (Box 14)
      - Finals (Box 14)
    - Research
      - Clocks (Box 14)
      - Competitors (Box 14)
      - Sale data (Box 14)
      - Sales study (Box 14)
      - Sketches - not used (Box 14)
  - Gimbel's display fixtures (Box 14)
  - Glass and basketry (Box 14)
  - Glass making - factory notes (Box 14)
  - Glassware
    - Beverage (Box 14)
    - For glass and pottery (Box 14)
    - Merchandise data (Box 14)
    - Preliminary drawings (Box 14)
    - Seneca casual (Box 14)
  - Glaze diagrams, stoneware (Box 14)
  - Glue pen (Box 14)
  - Handler (Box 15)
  - Harper's (Box 15)
  - Harker
    - Ashtray (Box 15)
    - B+B plate (Box 15)
    - Bladder camdion (Box 15)
    - Clover pattern studies (Box 15)
      See Oversize material: Miscellaneous (Oversize 7).
    - Dandelion (Box 15)
    - Final drawings (Box 15)
    - Gravy boat (Box 15)
    - Honeysuckle (Box 15)
    - Ideas (Box 15)
    - Labels (Box 15)
    - New items (Box 15)
    - Pottery
      - Cup trial, 2 folders (Box 15)
      - Theme A, Preliminary studies
        - Casserole (Box 15)
        - Cereal, soup (Box 15)
        - Coffee and teapot (Box 15)
        - Cup and handles (Box 15)
        - Dessert bowl (Box 15)
        - Dinner plate (Box 15)
        - Meat plate (Box 15)
        - Salt and pepper (Box 15)
        - Sauce and gravy (Box 15)
        - Sugar and creamer (Box 15)
        - Vegetable dish and cover (Box 15)
      - Theme B, preliminary sketches
        - Coffee and teapot (Box 15)
        - Covered casserole (Box 15)
        - Dessert dish (Box 15)
        - Meat platter (Box 15)
        - Salt and pepper (Box 15)
        - Sauce and gravy (Box 15)
        - Sugar and creamer (Box 15)
        - Vegetable dish (Box 15)
  - Hull
    - Counter display (Box 15)
    - Cutlery box linings (Box 15)
    - Dinner fork studies (Box 15)
    - Dinner knife studies (Box 15)
    - Factory drawings (Box 15)
    - Factory notes (Box 15)
    - Factory samples (Box 15)
    - Final drawings (Box 15)
    - Final presentation drawings (Box 15)
    - Flatware, general
      - Others (Box 15)
      - RW twist (Box 15)
      - General (Box 15)
    - Kitchen set holder prints (Box 15)
    - Knife, fork, spoon (Box 15)
    - Market research (Box 15)
    - Master model (Box 15)
    - Miscellaneous drawings (Box 15)
    - New items (Box 15)
    - Notes for, 1954 (Box 15)
    - Packaging
      - Carving sketches (Box 15)
      - Color (Box 15)
      - Kitchen set studies (Box 15)
      - Market research (Box 15)
      - Source research (Box 15)
      - Steakset studies (Box 15)
    - Preliminary studies (Box 15)
    - Presentation renderings (Box 15)
    - Production notes (Box 16)
    - Progress schedule (Box 16)
    - Research for ICT (Box 16)
    - Salad fork studies (Box 16)
    - Sample larger soup (Box 16)
    - Serving pieces (Box 16)
    - Serving spoon (Box 16)
    - Serving spoon studies (Box 16)
    - Stainless flatware (Box 16)
    - Stainless flatware packaging (Box 16)
    - Stainless flatware sketches and notes (Box 16)
    - Steak knife packaging (Box 16)
    - Tracings (Box 16)
    - Wood finishes (Box 16)
    - Woods research (Box 16)
  - Hunt Foods and Industries
    - Conference (Box 16)
    - Design (Box 16)
    - Drafting (Box 16)
    - Research
      - Caps (Box 16)
      - Data (Box 16)
      - Extra copies (Box 16)
      - Finished interview (Box 16)
      - Labeling, 2 folders (Box 16)
      - Original interviews (Box 16)
      - Photographs (Box 16)
      - Plastic squeeze bottle (Box 16)
      - Preliminary (Box 16)
      - Report on research conferences (Box 16)
      - Summaries (Box 16)
      - Survey analysis (Box 16)
      - Survey summary (Box 16)
      - Survey working information (Box 16)
  - Ideal Toy Company
    - Classic plastics (Box 16)
    - Classic plastics drawings (Box 16)
    - Classic plastics roughs (Box 16)
    - Idealware
      - Autographs (Box 16)
      - Notes (Box 16)
      - Photos (Box 16)
      - Renderings (Box 16)
      - Renderings, watering cans (Oversize 46)
    - Ideas (Box 16)
    - Insulated tumbler (Box 16)
    - Salt and pepper (Box 16)
    - Water can (Box 16)
    - Water pitcher (Box 16)
  - Imperial Glass Company
    - 54 [1954?] (Box 16)
    - Aggregate text studies (Box 16)
    - Aggregate text templates (Box 16)
    - Colored pressed presentation drawings (Box 16)
    - Conference notes (Box 16)
    - Factory notes (Box 16)
    - Final drawings (Box 16)
    - New ideas (Box 16)
    - Seed glass, final presentation drawings, original sketches, studies; 3 folders (Box 16)
    - Twist pattern, original sketches, presentation sketches, templates (Box 16)
  - Indiana
    - Beverage (Box 17)
    - Beverage themes (Box 17)
    - Gift theme 1 (Box 17)
    - Gift theme 3 (Box 17)
    - Gift themes (Box 17)
    - Notes (Box 17)
    - Review sketches (Box 17)
  - Instrument rack (Box 17)
  - Intaglio set (Box 17)
  - International appliance (Box 17)
    See also Oversize material: Miscellaneous (Oversize 8).
  - International handkerchief (Box 17)
  - Iroquois China Company
    - [General], 2 folders (Box 17)
    - 1952 A.D. cup and saucer (Box 17)
    - 1956 changes (Box 17)
    - Added pieces (Box 17)
    - Band decoration (Box 17)
    - Bandana (Box 17)
    - Basketry designs (Box 17)
    - Butter dish (Box 17)
    - Casual Perf. "metal wire trays" (Box 17)
    - Casual Perf. Preliminary drawings (Box 17)
    - Contemplated ideas for decoration (Box 17)
    - Cup - 1963 and, 1964 (Box 17)
    - Cup and sugar (Box 17)
    - Decorated, 2 folders (Box 17)
    - Decorated casserole (Box 17)
    - Decorated creamer (Box 17)
    - Decorated cup (Box 17)
    - Decorated food warmer (Box 17)
    - Decorated preliminary photo stats (Box 17)
    - Decorated salt cellars (Box 17)
    - Decorated teapot (Box 17)
    - Decorated tureen, 2 folders (Box 17)
    - Decoration (Box 17)
    - Decoration, preliminary (Box 17)
    - Decoration, test stamp (Box 17)
    - Design, nasturtiums (Box 17)
      See also Oversize material: Miscellaneous (Oversize 6).
    - Design and drawings (Box 17)
    - Designs and sketches (Box 17)
    - Display studies (Box 17)
    - Drawings (Box 17)
    - Drawings and color (Box 17)
    - Electric tray (Box 17)
    - Fifty - eight color (Box 17)
    - Final drawings (Box 17)
    - Final drawings of new items (Box 17)
    - Fruit (Box 17)
    - Glaze formulae (Box 17)
    - Gravy bowl (Box 17)
    - Gumbo (Box 17)
    - Heaters (Box 17)
    - Logo (Box 17)
    - Mixing pitcher (Box 17)
    - Mug (Box 17)
    - New plate (Box 17)
    - Notes on factory visit (Box 17)
    - Notes on presentation (Box 18)
    - Open vegetable (Box 18)
    - Pattern finals (Box 18)
    - Patterns - roughs of patterns submitted (Box 18)
    - Pepper mill, salt shakers (Box 18)
    - Presentation renderings (Box 18)
    - Presentation renderings, new items, See Oversize material: Miscellaneous (Oversize 8).
    - Rattan drawings (Box 18)
    - Rattan racks (Box 18)
    - Revisions (1959) (Box 18)
    - Sketches (Box 18)
    - Stove and pitcher (Box 18)
    - Sugar and cover (Box 18)
    - Suggestions for new colors (Box 18)
    - Tureens (Box 18)
    - TV plate (Box 18)
    - Underglaze (Box 18)
    - Wire job (Box 18)
    - Wrought iron and barbecue items (Box 18)
  - Jamestown Type, period studies 1 + 2 (Box 18)
  - Jayme Products, Inc. (Box 18)
  - Jewelry (Box 18)
  - Juice pitcher (Box 18)
  - Klise Woodenware
    - [General] (Box 18)
    - Drafting - M.W. + R.W. sketches, 2 folders (Box 18)
  - [Edwin M.] Knowles China Company:
    - Design
      - Azalea (Box 18)
      - Baby's breath (Box 18)
      - Baby's breath roughs, 2 folders (Box 18)
      - Back stamp (Box 18)
      - Blue lace (Box 18)
      - Botanica, See Oversize material: Miscellaneous (Oversize 4).
      - Botanical roughs (Box 18)
      - Centerpiece (Box 18)
      - Dandelion (Box 18)
      - Delphinium (Box 18)
      - Esquire, See Oversize material: Miscellaneous (Oversize 4).
      - Factory notes (Box 18)
      - Final drawings (Box 18)
      - Gravy boat (Box 18)
      - "Lace" final art (Box 18)
      - Lace flower (Box 18)
      - Lace roughs (Box 18)
      - Lace sketches, rejected (Box 18)
      - "Loop " roughs (Box 18)
      - New items, final drawings (Box 18)
      - Patterns rejected (Box 18)
      - Preliminary sketches (Box 18)
      - Rejected art decorations (Box 18)
      - Rejected art sketches (Box 18)
      - Roughs (Box 19)
      - Rejected idea (Box 19)
      - Seed (Box 19)
      - Shapes (Box 19)
      - Solar (Box 19)
      - Teapot finals (Box 19)
      - Templates
        - Covered sugar (Box 19)
        - New covered sugar (Box 19)
        - Shapes (Box 19)
        - Teapot (Box 19)
    - Drafting
      - Décor sketches (Box 19)
      - Display revisions (Box 19)
      - Fern roughs (Box 19)
      - Final drawings (Box 19)
      - Grass final art (Box 19)
      - Grass pattern (Box 19)
      - Pattern suggestions (Box 19)
      - "Pink Buttercup" (Box 19)
      - "Seed" design roughs (Box 19)
      - "Seed" pattern, final artwork (Box 19)
      - Sketches (Box 19)
      - Solar (Box 19)
      - Thread pattern (Box 19)
    - Notes (Box 19)
    - Old account
      - Dinnerware details (Box 19)
      - Shape studies (Box 19)
    - Research (Box 19)
    - Research, old shapes (Box 19)
    - Sample (Box 19)
    - Sample decoration, 2 folders (Box 19)
  - Kosta Glass
    - Mexican glass (Box 20)
    - Renderings (Box 20)
      See also Oversize material: Miscellaneous (Oversize 4).
    - Rough sketches (Box 20)
    - Roughs (Box 20)
  - Lamp (Box 20)
  - Lamps (Box 20)
  - Lantern slides (Box 20)
  - Laundry basket (Box 20)
  - Leacock and Company
    - Accepted designs, See Oversize material: Miscellaneous (Oversize 22).
    - Leacock winter (Box 20)
    - Linens (Box 20)
    - Winter tablecloth and napkins (Oversize 31)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 20)
  - Lily pattern
    - Backstamp (Box 20)
    - Final drawings (Box 20)
    - Master model (Box 20)
  - Line details500 (Box 20)
  - Lloyd Manufacturing
    - [General] (Box 20)
    - Fibre furniture (Box 20)
  - Long-Bell
    - Abacca door (Box 20)
    - Appliance storage, 2 folders (Box 20)
    - Back of door (Box 20)
    - Cleaning center (Box 20)
    - Conference notes (Box 20)
    - D plates + cups + vegetable (Box 20)
    - Field trip notes (Box 20)
    - Glass door (Box 20)
    - Hutch adapter (Box 20)
    - Pan file (Box 20)
    - Presentation (Box 20)
    - Questionnaire, 2 folders (Box 20)
    - Resources (Box 20)
  - Madison Glass
    - Finished tracings (Box 20)
    - Presentation drawings (Box 20)
  - Mallory-Randall Corporation
    - [General] (Box 20)
    - Research (Box 20)
  - McCall's
    - Bedroom
      - Boys and girls (Box 20)
      - Color studies (Box 20)
      - Furniture sketches (Box 20)
      - Layout (Box 20)
      - Master (Box 20)
      - Studies, plans and elevations (Box 20)
    - Finals (Box 20)
    - Furniture details (Box 20)
    - Living room and dining room (Box 20)
    - Notes and sketches (Box 20)
    - One room apartment (Box 20)
    - Plan and elevation (Box 20)
    - Setting for easier living (Box 20)
  - Meat platter (Box 20)
  - Mental cripple (Box 20)
  - Merganthaler Linotype Company, 2 folders (Box 20)
  - Metalware (Box 20)
  - Metropolitan Museum of Art, basket (Box 20)
  - Metro Tile and Marble Company (Box 20)
  - Milius Shoe Company (Box 20)
  - Modern Age (Box 20)
  - Morgantown Glass
    - Factory drawings (Box 21)
    - Glass samples (Box 21)
    - Glass ware (Box 21)
    - Martini bottle (Box 21)
    - Moonstone types (Box 21)
    - Optic types (Box 21)
    - Pilsner studies (Box 21)
    - Plain transparent (Box 21)
    - Stemware, 2 folders (Box 21)
    - Stemware
      - Designs (Box 21)
      - New sketches (Box 21)
      - Notes (Box 21)
      - Old sketches (Box 21)
      - Templates (Box 21)
  - Nasturtium (Box 21)
  - National Silver
    - Backstamp (Box 21)
    - Corn (Box 21)
    - German stainless (Box 21)
    - Holloware research (Box 21)
    - Holloware templates (Box 21)
    - Items flatware (Box 21)
    - Lily serving pieces (Box 21)
    - Lily sketches (Box 21)
    - New stainless (Box 21)
    - Pinch (Box 21)
    - Pinch service sketches (Box 21)
    - Plastic handled flatware (Box 21)
    - Plastic handled sketches (Box 21)
    - Presentation negatives (Box 21)
    - Silverplate sketches (Box 21)
    - Silverplated flatware (Box 21)
    - Sketches, June, 1956; 2 folders (Box 21)
    - Sketches, lily (Box 21)
    - Sketches, presentation (Box 21)
    - Stainless flatware (Box 21)
    - Stainless flatware notes (Box 21)
    - Stainless flatware, June, 1956 (Box 21)
    - Stainless sketches (Box 21)
    - Sterling flatware (Box 21)
    - Teapot sketch (Box 21)
  - New York World's Fair
    - [General], 2 folders (Box 21)
    - Float (Box 21)
    - Focal food exhibit, 2 folders (Box 21)
      See also World's Fair, New York, and Oversize material: Miscellaneous (Oversize 23).
    - Market bulletin (Box 21)
    - Photographs (Box 21)
      See also Oversize material: Miscellaneous (Oversize 1).
  - Northern Industrial Chemical Company (NIC)
    - Backstamp studies, 2 folders (Box 21)
    - Bow knot final decoration (Box 21)
    - Box (Box 21)
    - Box correction (Box 21)
    - Brochure roughs (Box 21)
    - BS general preliminary studies (Box 21)
    - Color experiments (Box 21)
    - Conference notes (Box 21)
    - Cup creamer studies (Box 21)
    - Decorated color (Box 21)
    - Dinner plate studies (Box 21)
    - Display box (Box 21)
    - Display cup (Box 21)
    - Drawings and templates before revision (Box 21)
    - Experimental dinnerware (Box 21)
    - Flair dinnerware illustrations, See Oversize material: Miscellaneous (Oversize 23).
    - Final drafts (Box 21)
    - Final pink cosmos (Box 21)
    - Final templates (Box 21)
    - Finished drawings (Box 21)
    - Items (Box 21)
    - Large soup (Box 21)
    - New patterns (Box 21)
    - New shapes (Box 21)
    - New soup, sugar (Box 21)
    - New sugar tumbler (Box 21)
    - Original mechanical drawings (Box 21)
    - Pink cosmos roughs (Box 21)
    - Plaster models - dinnerware (Box 21)
    - Platter studies (Box 21)
    - Preliminary templates (Box 21)
    - Rejected drawing (Box 21)
    - Residential (Box 21)
    - Residential and Flair (Box 21)
      See also Oversize material: Miscellaneous (Oversize 23).
    - Rough decorations (Box 21)
    - Saucer B+B (Box 21)
    - Soup and sugar studies (Box 21)
    - Spottle BBQ line (Box 21)
    - Tumbler studies (Box 21)
    - Tumbler sugar bowl (Box 21)
    - Unmarked, 2 folders (Box 21)
    - Vegetable cover studies (Box 21)
  - Notes, interior design (Box 22)
  - Old Hickory
    See also American Modern: Design studies.
    - Catalogue data (Box 22)
    - Iroquois (Box 22)
    - Details (Box 22)
    - Drawings (Box 22)
    - Furniture sketches (Box 22)
    - Our drawings (Box 22)
    - Sketches (Box 22)
    - Studies, 2 folders (Box 22)
  - Opening coliseum show (Box 22)
  - Outdoor furniture (Box 22)
  - Paden City Glassware Company
    - Chowder bowls (Box 22)
    - Covered pitcher (Box 22)
    - Dinnerware (Box 22)
    - Factory drawings (Box 22)
    - Glass cover production notes (Box 22)
    - New items (Box 22)
    - New items for, 1952 (Box 22)
    - New items salt and pepper (Box 22)
    - New items plaster models (Box 22)
  - Paden City Pottery
    - A.D. coffee cup (Box 22)
    - Chop plate (Box 22)
    - Cup (Box 22)
    - Dinner plate (Box 22)
    - Platter (Box 22)
    - Salad bowl (Box 22)
    - Sugar, creamer (Box 22)
    - Theme 2 final drawings (Box 22)
    - Theme 7 final drawings (Box 22)
    - Tumblers, vegetable bowl and cover (Box 22)
  - Paden City studies (Box 22)
  - Painting
    - Esquire (Box 22)
    - Fantasy (Box 22)
  - Paper Novelty (Box 22)
    See also Oversize material: Miscellaneous (Oversize 16).
  - Patchogue (Box 22)
  - Patchogue Plymouth Mills ugs (Box 22)
  - Patents (Box 22)
  - Patterns for cut-outs (Box 22)
  - Pelican cooler (Box 22)
  - Penn. Dutch and colonial (Box 22)
  - Peerless Electricity, Inc., Broil-Quick
    See also Broil Quick (above) as well as Oversize material: Miscellaneous (Oversize 16) and Oversize material: Miscellaneous (Oversize 18).
    - Accessories (Box 22)
    - Dial studies (Box 22)
    - Drafting, construction, diagrams (Box 22)
    - Drawings (Box 22)
    - Drawings and color samples (Box 22)
    - Drawings, final (Box 22)
    - Drawings, preliminary (Box 22)
    - Elevator sketches (Box 23)
    - Lettering (Box 23)
    - Notes, 2 folders (Box 23)
    - Notes, special baking (Box 23)
    - Plastics (Box 23)
    - Sketches (Box 23)
    - Sketches I (Box 23)
    - Sketches II (Box 23)
    - Sketches, accepted accessories (Box 23)
  - Philadelphia room piano (Box 23)
  - Photos of plastic dinnerware (Box 23)
  - Plastic china (Box 23)
  - Plastic competitors (Box 23)
  - Plastic dinnerware (Box 23)
  - Plastic everyday ware (Box 23)
  - Plastic every day ware, tracings, 2 folders (Box 23)
  - Plastics, pot sketches (Box 23)
  - Proctor & Gamble, 2 folders (Box 23)
  - Proctor & Gamble, Big Top
    - Capacity studies (Box 23)
    - Label placement studies (Box 23)
    - Premium sketches - plastic tray (Box 23)
    - Presentation (Box 23)
    - Rejected shapes (Box 23)
    - Number 2 shape (Box 23)
    - Number 3 shape (Box 23)
    - Number 4 shape (Box 23)
    - Number 5 shape (Box 23)
    - Number 6 shape (Box 23)
    - Number 7 shape (Box 23)
    - Number 8 shape (Box 23)
    - Number 9 shape (Box 23)
  - Proctor and Gamble conference notes (Box 23)
  - Proctor and Gamble kitchen (Box 23)
  - Proctor and Gamble shapes (Box 23)
    - Before capacity (Box 23)
    - Chosen for testing (Box 23)
    - Presented (Box 23)
  - Rattan carts and carriers (Box 23)
  - Ravenware
    - Beverage service (Box 23)
    - Bowls (Box 23)
    - Bun warmer (Box 23)
    - Chafing dish (Box 23)
    - Cheese board (Box 23)
    - Cheese knife (Box 23)
    - Coffee service (Box 23)
    - Competition (Box 23)
    - Design presentation (Box 23)
    - Electric trivet (Box 23)
    - Factory drawing (Box 23)
    - Final drawing (Box 23)
    - Food themes (Box 23)
    - Handles and knobs (Box 23)
    - Ice bucket, 2 folders (Box 23)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 23)
    - Model chafing dish (Box 23)
    - Notes (Box 23)
    - Presentation (Box 23)
    - Presentation, pewter designs, See Oversize material: Miscellaneous (Oversize 17).
    - Rectangular tray (Box 23)
    - Relish (Box 23)
    - Research (Box 23)
    - Roundtray (Box 23)
    - Unmarked (Box 23)
  - Raymor Manufacturing Division
    - Accessories (Box 23)
    - Lamp photos (Box 23)
    - Lamps, floor (Box 23)
    - Lamps, table (Box 23)
    - Lamps, table old (Box 23)
  - Residential Melmac (Box 24)
  - Revolutionary cup and saucer (Box 24)
  - Rittenhouse chimes (Box 24)
  - Roker design (Box 24)
  - Rubenstein, Helena (Box 24)
  - Rubenstein, Helena, department store window (Box 24)
  - Rustic dinnerware renderings (Box 24)
  - Sales, 4 folders (Box 24)
  - Samsonite catalogues (Box 24)
  - Samsonite outdoor chairs (Box 24)
  - Sauce bowl studies (Box 24)
  - Schmid International
    - Back stamp and names (Box 24)
    - Factory drawings (Box 24)
    - Gravies (Box 24)
    - Lacquer (Box 24)
    - Opaline (Box 24)
    - Porcelain, final factory drawings (Box 24)
    - Porcelain, preliminary (Box 24)
    - Porcelain, sketches (Box 24)
    - Prints, woodware (Box 24)
    - Stoneware (Box 24)
    - Stoneware factory drawings (Box 24)
  - Sears, Roebuck & Company "knockdown"
    - Furniture, 3 folders (Box 24)
      See also Oversize material: Miscellaneous (Oversize 18).
    - Final drawings, bedroom furniture, 1942; 1954; 2 folders (Box 24)
    - Notes, field trip [to] Sears stores local (Box 24)
  - Seavey and Chapleau glassware (Box 24)
  - Seven inch plate and saucer (Box 24)
  - Sharon Steel Corporation (Box 24)
  - Showroom (Box 24)
  - Shun Lee, Shun Lee Palace is a restaurant located at 155 East 55th Street in New York City; Wright designed every element of the restaurant
    - Canopy, sign and door pull (Box 24)
    - Coffee cup (Box 24)
    - Flatware (Box 24)
    - Lacquer (Box 24)
    - Linens (Box 24)
    - Orders (Box 24)
    - Plastic and lacquer (Box 24)
    - Renovations (Box 24)
    - Restaurant correspondence and invoices (Box 24)
    - Restaurant renovations (Box 24)
    - Spoon (Box 24)
    - Waiter stands (Box 24)
  - Shun Li [Lee]
    - Related sketching and drafting (Box 24)
    - Silver (Box 24)
    - Table accessories (Box 24)
  - Shwayder Brothers, Inc.
    - Analysis and research (Box 25)
    - Analysis and research, 1949-1951 (Oversize 13)
    - Captain's chair
      - Final drawing (Box 25)
      - Sketches (Box 25)
    - Chair renderings, See Oversize material: Miscellaneous (Oversize 11).
    - Chair, folding/outdoor furniture, 13 folders (Box 25)
    - Color
      - Final wood (Box 25)
      - Research folder (Box 25)
      - Upholstery (Box 25)
    - Competition (Box 25)
    - Design for outdoor chair (Box 25)
    - Existing frame colors (Box 25)
    - Folding furniture, chair
      - Cardboard model (Box 25)
      - Folding construction (Box 25)
      - Folding metal design (Box 25)
      - Folding metal and plywood (Box 25)
    - Folding furniture, table
      - Mechanism (Box 25)
      - Plywood (Box 25)
    - Luggage
      - Hangers (Box 25)
      - Final hardware (Box 25)
      - Samsonite - decal (Box 25)
      - Samsonite - final drawing (Box 25)
    - Presentation material (Box 25)
    - School designs, 6 folders (Box 26)
    - School desks (Box 26)
    - School final drawings, 4 folders (Box 26)
    - School furniture
      - Anatomical research (Box 26)
      - Factory notes (Box 27)
      - Final drawing (Box 27)
      - Institutional furniture
        - Color and finish (Box 27)
        - Color research (Box 27)
        - Competition (Box 27)
        - Construction (Box 27)
        - Sketches (Box 27)
      - Leg details (Box 27)
      - Material research (Box 27)
      - Photostats (Box 27)
      - Preliminary drawings (Box 27)